Dylan Wilson

Benjamin Russell Court, 29 Grasmere St, Leicester LE2 7PT Email: 2002.dylanwilson@gmail.com Mobile: 07456445701

Personal Profile

An adaptive 3rd year Computer Science undergraduate seeking experience in the catering industry. 4 months employed programming and a year of retail experience. Well versed in Python, Java, and PHP with adept knowledge of HTML and JavaScript.

Key Skills

Excellent software programming: developed over the 7 years of programming experience both in and out of education. This was enhanced further over the course of my first year attending university.

Written Documentation: During my first term, I had to write multiple essays as well as document my code.

Problem solving: This was developed during my programming module as well as my work experience.

Great Computer Science Knowledge: an overall understanding of computer science was achieved whilst completing my first and second year of my BSc.

Communication Skills: excellent at working well within a team environment as well as talking to customers with challenging accents or difficulties.

Education

De Montfort University, Leicester BSc (Hons) Computer Science Oct 2020- Present

- 79.625%	Year 2 Modules	- 74.25%	
- 66%	Software and Security Management		-58%
- 94%	Object Oriented Design		-96%
- 56%	Web Application Development		-63%
- 82%	Object Oriented Development		-76%
- 62%	Concurrent and parallel Algorithms		-77%
- 80%	Agile Team Development		-83%
Computer Law and Cyber Security - 72%		Data Structures and Algorithms	
Database Design and Implementation-65%		Introduction to Research	
	- 66% - 94% - 56% - 82% - 62% - 80% urity - 72%	 - 66% Software and Security - 94% Object Oriented Design - 56% Web Application Development - 82% Object Oriented Development - 62% Concurrent and paralle - 80% Agile Team Development - 30% Data Structures and Alle 	 - 66% Software and Security Management - 94% Object Oriented Design - 56% Web Application Development - 82% Object Oriented Development - 62% Concurrent and parallel Algorithms - 80% Agile Team Development Data Structures and Algorithms

Year 3 Modules

-Pending
-Pending
-Pending
-Pending
-75%
-66%
-71%

Finham Park School, Coventry Sep 2013-2018

A-Levels in 3 Subjects (ADD) - Computer Science, Mathematics and Physics respectively Sep 2018-2020

GCES's in 10 subjects (7-4) Mathematics 7, Science (7,7), English Language 5

Work Experience

Warwick Manufacturing Group, Research Assistant July 2021- September 2021, January 2021 – February 2021 Coventry

- Programmed in JavaScript, HTML and Python to create a VR Showroom for automotive vehicles.
- Used and compared different 3D laser scanners to determine which option would be best for the MOD.
- Created an online database where users can book a piece of equipment for an extended amount of time as well as inputting a backlog of data 6 months prior to my start date.

Earlsdon Post Office and Convenience Store, Customer Assistant January 2020 – September 2020, May 2021 - September 2021, Coventry

- Provided support and advice to customers on products and services around the store.
- Setup displays and merchandise on the shop floor.
- Managed the electronic till and handled cash payments allowing me to use my mental arithmetic skills.
- Worked in a fast-paced environment and multi-tasked to ensure all duties were completed on time.

The Soar Point, Bar/Kitchen Team Member

October2022- Present, Leicester

- Provided support and advice to customers on products and services around the bar.
- Setup and maintain facilities accessible to the customer.
- Managed the electronic till and handled cash payments.
- Worked in a fast-paced environment and multi-tasked to ensure all duties were completed on time.
- Worked within a kitchen environment and learnt the basics for food hygiene and cleanliness.

Additional Achievements

Achieved the following awards:

- Duke of Edinburgh Bronze award, Silver pending
- Chief Scout Platinum award, Diamond pending
- National Citizenship Service
- Gold industrial cadet award

Hobbies and interests

Active Member of DMU climbing society and on the committee as the Health and Safety Officer. I have represented DMU in national esports competitions. Volunteer scout leader with 70th Coventry scout group, planning and leading beavers, cubs, and scouts in activities. Enjoy dingy sailing and a variety of other water sports.

References available upon request.